The famous high school detective Shinichi Kudo
أجبرت منظمة ما المُتحري الشهير ،في الثانوية، كودو شينتشي
was forced to take a strange poison by a certain organization,
على تجرّع سم غريب
causing him to shrink and become Conan Edogawa!
!فتقلّص جسده وأصبح إيدوغاوا كونان
Doesn't matter if I'm small!
!لا يهم صغر بنيتي
My mind's that of a brilliant 17-year-old detective!
!فدماغي ذاك لمُتحرٍّ في السابعة عشر
I'll solve another case today that would have adults shaking in their boots!
سأحلّ قضيّة أخرى تستعصي !على البالغين اليوم
Secret Treasures of the World Exhibit
معرض كنوز العالم السرّية
It's so pretty!
!جميل
Totally awesome!
!هذا مُذهل
Amazing!
!مبهر
A map to buried treasure?
خريطة كنز مدفون؟
That sure was fun!
كان ذلك مُسلياً
I really liked that gold mask!
أعجبني ذاك القناع الذهبي كثيراً
There's still tons of secret treasure all over the world
لا تزال هناك كنوز كثيرة حول العالم
that hasn't been discovered yet!
لم تُكتشف بعد
For reals?! I wanna try and find some!
!صدقاً؟ أريد البحث عن واحد
What's this?
ما هذا؟
What is it?
ماذا هناك؟
What's with this piece of paper?
ما خطب هذه الورقة؟
It has a bunch of strange symbols on it...
بها عدّة رموز غريبة
Hey! Maybe it's a treasure map!
!لعلّها خريطة كنز
A treasure map?
خريطة كنز؟
Yeah, right!
غير معقول
What?! Are you sayin' you can't believe what Ayumi says?!
!ماذا؟! لا تصدّق كلام أيومي؟
But...
...لكن
But what?
لكن ماذا؟
What are you getting so mad about?
ما الذي يغضبكم هكذا؟
But what?!
!لكن ماذا؟
Let's go check it out!
!لنذهب لتفقد الأمر
I agree!
!أتفق
Yeah!
!أجل
Ayumi's definitely right about this!
!أيومي محقّة بلا شك
What if it really is a 100% genuine treasure map?!
ماذا لو كانت خريطة كنز حقيقية؟
Exactly! What if it is a real map?!
!بالفعل! ماذا لو كانت كذلك؟
So, let's go check it out!
!لنذهب ونرى
Definitely!
!تماماً
Alright then! Let's go treasure hunting!
!حسنٌ، لنذهب في رحلة بحث عن كنز
From this day forth we'll be known as the Junior Detective Club!
!نحن المتحرّيون الصغار من اليوم فصاعداً
Huh? Junior Detective Club?
ماذا؟ المتحرّيون الصغار؟
That sounds so cool!
!يبدو رائعاً
I, Genta Kojima, will be club leader!
!سأكون أنا، كوجيما غينتا، رئيس النادي
Any objections?!
أيّ اعتراضات؟
Nope!
!كلا
My head's starting to hurt...
...بدأ رأسي يؤلمني
Let's go!
!لنذهب
Yeah!
!أجل
Go where?
نذهب أين؟
Don't ask me...
...لا-لا أدري
Let me have a look at that piece of paper...
أروني تلك الورقة قليلاً
Look at this very top symbol.
انظروا للرمز العلوي
Haven't you seen this somewhere before?
ألم يسبق ورأيتموه في مكان؟
Hurry!
!بسرعة
Alright!
!أجل
Come on!
!هيّا
Dino Cavane, the Italian crime lord who was arrested last night
اُعتقل زعيم الجريمة الإيطالي دينو كافاني
at an apartment complex near Tokyo Tower, has so far refused to say anything.
،في مجمع شقق ليلة الأمس قرب برج طوكيو ويرفض الإدلاء بأقوال حتى الآن
The police are currently pursuing Cavane's accomplices,
تلاحق الشرطة الآن رفاق كافاني
but they have been unable to find any clues leading to their whereabouts.
لكنهم لم يجدوا دلائل تقودهم لمكانهم بعد
The location of the 15,000 Maple Leaf gold coins they stole
موقع الخمسة عشر ألف عملة ميبل ليف" ذهبية التي سرقوها"
is also unknown.
مجهول أيضاً
To Tokyo Tower
إلى برج طوكيو
I thought the Tokyo Tower was suspicious from the very beginning!
!اشتبهتُ ببرج طوكيو منذ البداية
Now the treasure is as good as ours!
!الكنز يكاد يكون لنا الآن
But what do you think these letters mean?
لكن ما معنى هذه الأحرف برأيكم؟
It says "ORO" here, but...
..."مكتوبٌ "أو آر أو
Oro? Orochi? (Giant serpent)
(أورو؟ أوروتشي؟ (أفعى عملاقة
I bet it's an abbreviation!
!لا بدّ أنه اختصار
The first O stands for ookii, which means big!
!أوّل "أو" هي اختصار لـ "أووكي" والتي تعني كبير
The R means rich!
!و"آر" تعني غنيّ من الإنجليزيّة
And the last O stands for otakara, which means treasure!
!بينما "أو" الأخيرة اختصار "أوتاكارا"، أي كنز
So, that means it's a big treasure that will make you rich!
!فذلك يعني كنزاً كبيراً سيجعلك ثريّاً
Wow! I didn't know you could read English, Mitsuhiko!
مُذهل! لم أعلم أنك تجيد !قراءة الإنجليزية يا ميتسوهيكو
Well, just a little.
حسناً، نوعاً ما
I bet it's a huge treasure!
!لا شكّ بأنه كنزٌ كبير
Hey now!
!أنتم
Alright! I'm gonna use that treasure to eat the world's best eel dishes!
حسنٌ! سأستعمل ذاك الكنز لأكل !أفضل أطباق الأنقليس في العالم
I'm gonna go around the world 100 times!
!سأذهب في جولة حول العالم مئة مرّة
I'm going to buy a space shuttle from NASA and go into space!
سأشتري أنا مكوكاً فضائياً من "ناسا" وأذهب للفضاء
What about you, Conan-kun?
ماذا عنك يا كونان-كن؟
I'll save it, I guess...
...أ-أظنني سأدّخره
You don't know how to have fun, do ya?
لا تعرف كيف تمرح
Well, excuse me.
أعتذر لذلك
Alright! Here we are!
!حسنٌ، ها نحن
All that's left is to decipher the code!
!تبقى حلّ الشفرات فقط
But none of the other symbols look like anything,
لكن جميع الرموز المتبقية ...لا تشبه شيئاً
That's it! It's the moon!
!وجدتُها! إنّه القمر
The treasure must be where the moon and Tokyo Tower line up like this!
الكنز موجود حيث يكون القمر وبرج طوكيو !في نفس الخط بالتأكيد
That can't be it.
ذلك غير ممكن
The moon's position changes everyday,
فموضع القمر يتغير يومياً
and I doubt you could specify exact locations with such simple drawings.
كما أشك بإمكانك تحديد مواقع دقيقة برسومات بسيطة كهذه
Then where is it?!
!أين هو إذاً؟
Conan-kun, did you figure anything out?
هل اكتشفت شيئاً يا كونان-كن؟
I was wondering if the other symbols are abbreviations for things.
كنتُ أتساءل إن ما كانت الرموز الأخرى اختصارات لأشياء
Like this symbol beneath the tower could be a hat.
الرمز تحت البرج مثلاً قد يكون قبعة
Beneath that might be underwear.
وما تحته قد يكون سروالاً داخلياً
The umbrella beneath that could be an emblem on a sweater or something.
بينما المظلة أسفلهما قد تكون شعاراً على سترة وما شابه
And the thing that links them all together...
...والشيء الذي يربطهم
A clothes store!
!متجر ثياب
But this isn't enough to really...
...لكن لا يكفي هذا لـ
Hurry!
!أسرعوا
H-Hey!
!ا-انتظروا
Find it!
!ابحثوا عنه
There has to be a clue in here somewhere!
!لا بدّ من وجود دليل في مكان هنا
Come on! Faster!
!هيّا! أسرع
Hey, stop it, you three!
!توقفوا أنتم الثلاثة
Get out!
!اخرجوا
Stupid little kids!
!أيّها المشاغبون
I never want to see you here again!
!لا أريد رؤيتكم مُجدداً
Looks like it didn't have to do with clothing stores after all...
يبدو أنّها لم تكن مرتبطة بمحلّ ملابس
Nope...
أجل
I sure am hungry...
أشعر بالجوع
Wanna go eat something?
تريدون أكل شيء؟
Sure.
أجل
Hey, why don't we stop by a bookstore?
ما رأيكم أن نمرّ بمتجر كتب؟
Stupid! You can't eat anything at a bookstore!
أحمق، لا يمكنك أكل شيء في متجر كتب
Just for a short while. Okay?
قليلاً فقط، حسناً؟
Whoa!
!مُذهل
Hey, check this out! It's hilarious!
!انظروا لهذا! إنّه مضحك
Yeah, it is!
!معك حق
O-R-O. ORO?
أو آر أو"، أو-آر-أو"
Was there such a word in English?
أكانت هناك كلمة كهذه في الإنجليزية؟
No luck, it's not in there...
لا فائدة، ليست هنا
Which means...
...مما يعني
Italian...
...الإيطالية
I really doubt it...
أشكّ في ذلك
Here it is!
!ها هي
Oro in Italian means gold!
!أو آر أو" تعني الذهب في الإيطالية"
Which means this code really does show where treasure is!
مما يعني أن هذا الرمز !يدلّ لمكان الكنز حقاً
The accomplices of the Italian crime lord Dino Cavane,
...رفاق زعيم الجريمة الإيطالي دينو كافاني
who was caught yesterday, are currently in Japan.
الذي اُعتقل بالأمس متواجدون في اليابان حالياً
The whereabouts of the 15,000 Maple Leaf coins they stole
موقع الخمسة عشر ألف عملة ...ورق القيقب" ذهبية التي سرقوها"
are, as of yet, unknown.
لا يزال مجهولاً
These coins, which total over 600 million in Japanese yen, were...
العملات التي تتجاوز قيمتها ستمئة ...مليون ينّ ياباني كانت قد
600 million, huh? These guys must know what they're doing.
ستّمئة مليون؟ يعرفون ما يفعلون
You've trashed the place up again?!
!ترمي القمامة في المكان مجدداً؟
Can you get any worse?!
!لا أمل منك
That reminds me, where's the runt?
بالمناسبة، أين ذاك الفتى؟
If you mean Conan-kun, he left early this morning
إن كنتَ تقصد كونان-كن فقد غادر في الصباح الباكر
to go to the art museum with his friends.
للذهاب لمعرض الفنون مع أصدقائه
Kids sure got it easy.
الأطفال في نعيم حقّاً
Come on, Dad! At least help clean up a little!
!أبي! ساعدني بالتنظيف على الأقل
Fine, fine.
حسناً، حسناً
According to Italian authorities,
،وفقاً للشرطة الإيطالية
three of Cavane's accomplices are on the run, and one of them is Japanese.
ثلاثة من رفاق كافاني طليقون حالياً، وأحدهم يابانيّ
What's up with Conan-kun?
ما خطب كونان-كن؟
How should I know? That's all he's been doing since we got here!
كيف لي أن أعرف؟ كان ذلك كلّ ما يفعله مذ وصلنا
Do you think maybe he figured something out?
لعلّه اكتشف شيئاً
It's hopeless! I can't figure it out!
لا فائدة، لا أستطيع حلّها
What is this code?!
ما هذه الشفرة؟
Is it a map? Or is it some kind of message?!
أهي خريطة؟ أم رسالة ما؟
Darn it!
!تبّاً
Look!
!انظروا
Could that be it?!
أيمكن أنها تلك؟
See! That sign! It looks just like the 2nd symbol!
!تلك اللافتة! تشبه الرمز الثاني تماماً
Hey, it does!
معك حق
Which means...
...مما يعني
Could these symbols actually represent...?
...هذه الرموز لعلها تمثل
It has to be! This shop's directly in front of Tokyo Tower,
لا بد أنّها هي! هذا المتجر أمام برج طوكيو تماماً
and the next symbol has the shape of this sign!
!ويحمل الرمز التالي شكل هذه اللافتة
So, if we follow this order of store signs, we'll find the treasure!
!إن اتبعنا ترتيب لافتات المتاجر هذا إذاً، سنصل الكنز
But which way should we go from here?
لكن أين نذهب من هنا؟
Moon View Street!
!شارع منظر القمر
I bet it does! Let's go!
!بالتأكيد كذلك! هيّا بنا
Look! There it is!
!انظروا! ها هي
An upside-down triangle sign!
!لافتة مثلّث مقلوب
You're right! It looks just like the third symbol!
!بالفعل! كالرمز الثالث تماماً
So, these symbols really do represent...
...هذه الرموز تمثل بالفعل إذاً
An aquarium!
!معرض مائي
That's it! I figured it out!
!ها هي! وجدتُها
This code is a map from Tokyo Tower to the Nanbu Aquarium!
هذه الشفرة خريطة من برج طوكيو إلى معرض نانبو المائي
They drew the signs and displays of stores along Moon View Street!
رسموا شعارات ولافتات المتاجر !على شارع منظر القمر
And the final destination...
...والوجهة الأخيرة
...is a mountain of treasure!
!جبل كنز
Okay! Let's go!
!حسنٌ! لننطلق
Yeah!
!أجل
I didn't see the 5th star-shaped symbol anywhere...
لم أرَ رمز النجمة الخامس في أيّ مكان
Darn! And we were so close to the treasure!
!تبّاً! كنا قريبين جدّاً للكنز
Huh?
ماذا؟
We've made it all the way to the aquarium!
!وصلنا المعرض المائي
How can this be?!
كيف هذا؟
We never even found the 5th symbol on Moon View Street
لم نجد الرمز الخامس على شارع منظر القمر
between Tokyo Tower and the Nanbu Aquarium!
بين برج طوكيو ومعرض نانبو المائي
Or am I assuming something incorrectly?
أم هناك خلل في استنتاجي؟
Wait. Why is "gold" written in Italian?
لحظة، لمَ كُتب "الذهب" باللغة الإيطالية؟
If the person who wrote this was Italian, then the moon symbol...
...إن كان من كتب هذه شخص إيطالي، فرمز القمر
Could it be...?
...أيمكن
That's it! I figured it out!
!هكذا إذاً! فهمت
We need to go back to where we started!
!لنرجع لمكان بدايتنا
Hey! Conan!
!انتظر! كونان
It's hard to think that the person who wrote "gold" in Italian
من الصعب اعتقاد أنّ شخصاً كتب "ذهب" بالإيطالية
would use the moon symbol to represent Moon View Street,
سيستعمل رمز القمر لتمثيل شارع منظر القمر
which is in Japanese!
!المُسمى باليابانية
The moon represents night and the things you can only see at night!
القمر يمثل الليل والأشياء التي لا تراها سوى ليلاً
Neon signs!
!لافتات النيون
Conan! What did you figure out?
كونان! ما الذي اكتشفته؟
The neon sign in the 2nd symbol is over there!
!لافتة نيون في الرمز الثاني هي تلك
There!
!ها هو
You're right!
!معك حق
Next we go down by the stadium!
!سنذهب لذاك الملعب تالياً إذاً
We just need to find an umbrella-shaped sign!
!علينا إيجاد لافتة بشكل مظلة فقط
I don't see any umbrella-shaped signs anywhere...
لا أرى أيّ لافتة نيون بشكل مظلة
Are you sure you've got it right?
أأنت متأكد من استنتاجك؟
I already found it.
وجدتُها بالفعل
Tomorrow's Weather
طقس الغد
There.
هناك
What're you talking about? That's the sun.
ما الذي تقوله؟ إنّها الشمس
That's it! The symbol for rain!
!فهمت! رمز المطر
Rain must've been in the forecast for the day after they wrote the code!
كان توقع الطقس مطراً لليوم !الذي يعقب كتابتهم للشفرة
Next is a neon sign shaped like a star!
!التالي هو لافتة نيون بشكل نجم
I found it!
!وجدتُها
This has to be it!
!هذه هي بالتأكيد
A Ferris wheel!
!عجلة فيريس
There's no doubt about it! It's the 5th symbol!
!لا شكّ هناك! إنّه الرمز الخامس
So, we should see the 6th sign from here!
يُفترض أن نرى اللافتة السادسة من هنا إذاً
Where is it?!
!أين هي؟ أين؟
There it is! The 6th neon sign!
!تلك! لافتة النيون السادسة
Say, Conan, there's really gonna be treasure here, right?
كونان، يوجد كنز هنا حقاً، صحيح؟
Yeah. This symbol has "ORO" written next to it, after all.
أجل، فـ"أو آر أو" مكتوبة بجوار هذا الرمز
I've been looking for the last fish-shaped sign for a while,
كنتُ أبحث عن اللافتة بشكل السمكة الأخيرة
but I just can't seem to find it.
لكن لم أجدها بعد
Of course not.
بالطبع
The closest fish would probably be in a nearby river or something.
السمك الذي ستجده قد يكون في نهر قريب فقط
That's it! The river!
!ها هو! النهر
It must mean a river with fish in it!
!المقصود حتماً هو نهر يحتوي على سمك
Huh?
ماذا؟
Okay! Let's go check out the river!
!حسناً! لنذهب لتفقد النهر
Hey now!
!أنتم
Come on, Genta-kun! Stop!
يكفي يا غينتا-كن، توقف
That's dangerous, you know!
!هذا خطر
Quit yer yappin'! The treasure has to be at the bottom of this river!
!اصمتي! الكنز في قاع هذا النهر حتماً
Cold!
!بارد
No! This code represents things you can only see at night!
كلا! شفرة هذه الخريطة تحوي رموز أشياء تراها ليلاً فقط
So, the fish symbol at the end can't represent the river.
فلا يمكن أن يمثل رمز السمكة الأخير النهر
If my guess is correct, then it has to be somewhere nearby!
إن كان استنتاجي صحيحاً، فلا بد من وجودها بالقرب
A fish-shaped neon light...
ضوء نيون بشكل سمكة
Conan-kun?
كونان-كن
I finally found it.
وجدتُها أخيراً
The glowing fish, that is.
السمكة المضيئة
A glowing fish?
سمكة مضيئة؟
Never heard of any.
أين يوجد شيء كذاك؟
Just follow me.
اتبعوني فقط
Come on already...
...يا إلهي
Is there really gonna be a glowing fish here?!
أتوجد سمكة مضيئة هنا حقاً؟
Hey! It's so dark I can't see anything, much less any fish!
!أنت! لا تستطيع رؤية شيء في الظلام، فكيف بالسمك
Take a look outside.
انظروا للخارج من هنا
Towards that river.
نحو ذاك النهر
The river?
النهر؟
See! Over there!
!أترون؟ هناك
That's the glowing fish!
!تلك هي السمكة المضيئة
The lights are reflected on the water and make it look like a fish!
!الأنوار المعكوسة على الماء تشكّل منظر سمكة
And the fish's eye is the light on the building in front of us!
!وعين السمكة هي ضوء المبنى أمامنا
Does that mean the treasure's in here?!
!أي أن الكنز هنا؟
Yeah.
نعم
It's probably located right around...
...موقعه غالباً
...here!
هنا
A gold coin...
عملة ذهبية؟
What's that black shadow?!
ما ذاك الظلّ الأسود؟
It looks like it's connected to a rope.
يبدو أنّه مربوط بحبل
Now I see.
فهمت
They raised the sacks of gold coins up
رفعوا أكياس العملات الذهبية
by looping the rope around part of the ceiling that sticks out!
!بربط الحبل حول جزء بارز من السقف
It's the treasure!
!الكنز! إنّه الكنز
Thanks for the help, kiddos!
شكراً على المساعدة يا صغار
W-Who are you guys?
مـ-من أنتم؟
Weren't they the ones I saw in front of Tokyo Tower?
ألم يكونوا الأشخاص أمام برج طوكيو؟
Wait! Maybe they're the...
...أيمكن أنهم
Give it back! We found those first!
!أعده! نحن من وجدناه أولاً
Stop!
!توقف
Darn it!
!تبّاً
Are you alright, Genta-kun?
أأنت بخير يا غينتا-كن؟
I see. They still don't know where the coins are.
هكذا إذاً، لا يزالون يجهلون مكان العملات
Who are those people?
من هؤلاء الأشخاص؟
Members of that Italian crime ring, most likely!
أفراد عصابة إيطالية غالباً
Crime ring?!
!أفراد عصابة؟
Come to think of it, I heard about them on the news!
!صحيح، سمعت عنهم في أخبار التلفاز
That means those coins just now must've been--
...هذا يعني أنّ تلك العملات
That's right.
بالضبط
We swiped these coins from an Italian bank a year ago.
سرقنا تلك العملات من مصرف إيطالي قبل عام
Just like our Boss Cavane told us to.
كما أمرنا زعيمنا كافاني
But then he backstabbed us and ran off to Japan.
لكنّه خاننا وهرب لليابان
With the 15,000 Maple Leaf coins in tow, of course.
ومعه الخمسة عشر ألف عملة "ورق القيقب" بالطبع
We tailed him to Japan and paid him a visit!
!تعقّبناه لليابان وزرناه
But he had hidden the coins somewhere!
!لكن كان قد أخبأ العملات في مكانٍ ما سلفاً
He wouldn't tell us where he hid 'em, no matter how much we interrogated him.
رفض إخبارنا بالموقع رغم استجوابنا له عدّة مرّات
All we found at his place was this code!
كلّ ما وجدناه في غرفته هي هذه الشفرة
He wouldn't help us out, so we informed the police of his location,
رفض مساعدتنا فأخبرنا الشرطة بمكانه
and set out in search of the coins ourselves, relying only on his code.
وخرجنا للبحث عن العملات بأنفسنا بالاعتماد على هذه الشفرة
The wind blew the paper away when we stopped by the art museum.
قذفت الرّيح الورقةَ بعيداً عندما توقّفنا عند معرض الفنون
But we saw you cracking the code little by little,
لكنّنا رأيناكم تحلّون الشفرة رويداً رويداً
so we decided to let you keep going.
فقرّرنا السماح لكم بالمواصلة
Never imagined you'd actually find it for us though!
!لكن لم يخطر لنا أن تجدوه حقّاً
A gun!
!مـ-مسدس
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
So, tell me! Where are the coins?!
!أخبرني! أين العملات؟! أين؟
You better speak up!
!تكلّم فوراً
The fish.
السمكة
What?
ماذا؟
The coins are hidden at the location where the fish symbol
العملات مخبأة حيث يتطابق رمز السمكة
and the night view of the bridge outside match up!
مع المنظر الليلي للجسر خارجاً
I see.
فـ-فهمت
Conan! What'd you tell him for?!
كونان! لمَ أخبرتهم؟
We're as good as dead once they find the treasure!
سيتخلصون منا حتماً حالما يجدون الكنز
They're gonna kill us no matter what!
سيتخلّصون منا أيّاً يكن
They're gonna shoot us to death, I bet...
هل سيردوننا قتلى يا ترى؟
I bet they're gonna stick us in cement and drop us into the ocean...
سيغرقوننا بالإسمنت ويرموننا في المحيط بالتأكيد
No, they're going to burn us to death so there's no proof left behind!
كلا، سيحرقوننا حتى الموت كيلا يبقى أثر
Mom...
...أمّي
Dad...
...أبي
Mommy...
...ماما
It's too early to give up just yet!
من المبكر الاستسلام
We still have a chance!
لا تزال لدينا فرصة
If we all work together, that is!
!إن تكاتفنا بالطبع
How will that do anything?
ما يسعنا فعله؟
We're just children!
!نحن مجرد أطفال
Aren't we the Junior Detective Club?!
!ألسنا المتحريين الصغار؟
Alright! So, what do we do?
حسناً! ماذا علينا أن نفعل؟
Get up. But make sure they don't notice.
انهضوا، انتبهوا من أن يلاحظوكم
We only have one shot at this!
لدينا فرصة واحدة
The moment that they find the coins and let their guard down!
...حالما يجدون العملات ويتشتّت انتباههم
Now!
!الآن
Run!
!اركضوا
We did it!
!نجحنا
Afterward, we went straight to a nearby police station
توجّهنا لمركز شرطة قريب بعدها
and explained everything that had happened.
وشرحنا كلّ ما حدث
To everyone's delight, the gang was arrested and the case was closed.
اُعتقل أفراد العصابة وأُقفلت القضية
It wound up being the Junior Detective Club's very first accomplishment!
!وكان إنجازنا الأول لنا نحن، المتحرّيون الصغار
You're amazing! All of you!
أنتم مذهلون
I can't believe you cracked that code!
!حللتم تلك الشفرة
And you even captured some thieves!
!كما قبضتم على لصوص
It was me! I caught them!
!كان أنا! أنا قبضت عليهم
And I used my reasoning to decipher the code!
!وحللتُ الشفرة باستنتاجي
Don't listen to them!
لا تصغي لهما
It was Conan-kun who cracked the code and beat up the gang!
!كان كونان-كن من حلّ الشفرة وغلب العصابة
He was so cool!
!كان رائعاً جدّاً
Conan-kun.
كونان-كن
Kiss
قُبلة
Thank you!
!شكراً لك
Good for you, Conan-kun! You've made a cute little girlfriend!
!سررتُ لأجلك يا كونان-كن! حصلت على حبيبة ظريفة
N-No, I didn't...
!كـ-كلا
Now he's embarrassed! How cute!
!تحمر خجلاً! يا للظرافة
No, really!
!أخبرتك، كلا
Lousy Conan!
كونان الوغد
Darn it! There's still something I want to ask you!
!تبّاً! لا يزال هناك ما أريد سؤالكما عنه
Who has the bomb?!
من يحمل القنبلة؟
Huh? Where is it? I can't find--
...ماذا؟ أين هي؟ لا أستطيع
There's only one way to make her believe me!
هناك طريقة واحدة لجعلها تصدقني
If I tell her that I'm actually Shinichi Kudo!
!وهي أن أخبرها أنّي كودو سينتشي الحقيقي
Who are you really?
ما هويّتك بالضبط؟
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The Great Bullet Train Explosion.
انفجار قطار الطلقة الكبير
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Cell Phone.
هاتف خلوي
The next episode will keep you in suspense! Don't miss it!
الحلقة القادمة ستكون مثيرةً وحماسية أيضاً